<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alex&#39;s random blog</title>
    <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Alex&#39;s random blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 19:17:04 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://xieweialex.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 19:17:04 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>This is a page about &amp;ldquo;about me&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 19:17:04 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/test/</guid>
      <description>This is a Test</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What was I like 4 years ago</title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/4-years-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/4-years-ago/</guid>
      <description>All of a sudden everybody in the Wechat moments started recalling what was life like 4 years ago, then I realized today is the leap day for every 4 years.
What was I like 4 years ago on the leap day? I was in Shenzhen, just came back from my hometown Yueyang where I lost my luggage in a cab a few weeks ago. I was very disappointed, I never thought someone would seriously take my luggage and don&amp;rsquo;t return back, I even didn&amp;rsquo;t lock it (I still don&amp;rsquo;t lock my luggage during trips, I&amp;rsquo;m just a lazy, careless guy).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of the article &#34;The Feedback Fallacy&#34;</title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/the-feedback-fallacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/the-feedback-fallacy/</guid>
      <description>Here is the article The Feedback Fallacy Recently I read the article The Feedback Fallacy, I was amazed, I&amp;rsquo;ve thought it for a while, as I was raised in a traditional Asian culture which encourages submissiveness in a patriarchy way, I got a weak ego and incline to follow others whenever possible. But since I left my hometown and living alone in few metro cities for years, I found myself became more self-center, independent, and most importantly, happier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Post</title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 22:08:16 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/test-post/</guid>
      <description>Here is just some test text
what is funny isn&amp;rsquo;t funny</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/girl-i-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/girl-i-like/</guid>
      <description>Girl I like in the first sight There are some kind of girls I know I&amp;rsquo;d love to get in touch if possible in the first sight, what are those characters attract me? Let me clean my thought by write it down.
docile &amp;amp; diffidence I first heard this two words phrase from the Video, that&amp;rsquo;s the common stereotype of Japanese girls which lots of people like, yeah, shame to say, I&amp;rsquo;m one of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/i-love-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/i-love-work/</guid>
      <description>I love my work I always heard people saying &amp;ldquo;work life balance&amp;rdquo;, as a bachelor, I don&amp;rsquo;t have much personal life, it&amp;rsquo;s hard for me separate work and life. I heard Jeff bezos says &amp;ldquo;Work life harmony&amp;rdquo;, yes, I&amp;rsquo;m totally down with that.
I got paid constantly with considerable salary It&amp;rsquo;s hard to deny programmers got paid very decently nowadays comparing other profession, the market is booming, lots of opportunities available all the time, it&amp;rsquo;s a good time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/the-enjoyment-partial-blindness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/the-enjoyment-partial-blindness/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t get strapped by rules Recently just few months ago I started riding motorcycle, I knew it was pretty scary riding bike in this grueling Bay Area, but I knew I gonna love it, it was so much fun hitting on the road in a fast speed without a iron wrapper enclosed, I can feel the wind and road. As a beginner, I need to practice a lot to get use to ride on the two wheels, and the best and most difficult motorcycle practicing place is mountain road, luckily, there is a curvy mountain road close to my house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/thoughts-on-shawnshank-redemption/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/thoughts-on-shawnshank-redemption/</guid>
      <description>What I was touched by Shawnshank redemption Hope is a good thing, maybe the best thing in the world (with determination ) I&amp;rsquo;m not sure others, as for me, I&amp;rsquo;m really easy being touched by people made big success by long term continuse working, when I saw Andy open his arms in the raindrops embracing the baptism of new life after continuse dirty work in extremely condition, I was touched.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/why-not-panic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/why-not-panic/</guid>
      <description>Why don&amp;rsquo;t they panic Recently with the CoronaVirus tension ramps up, I started thinking about buy some face masks just in case, but both offline shops and online retailers all out of stock. Shit, I&amp;rsquo;ve seen numerous news about those Chinese guys
They have the basic trust in Government and news media It&amp;rsquo; quite ironic people in China they trust and rely on government so much, but every time any dire situation happens, they got in panic very fast and started looking all kinds of rumors.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>