<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alex&#39;s random blog</title>
    <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Alex&#39;s random blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 19:17:04 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://xieweialex.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 19:17:04 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>This is a page about &amp;ldquo;about me&amp;rdquo;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test</title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/test/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 19:17:04 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/test/</guid>
      <description>This is a Test</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What was I like 4 years ago</title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/4-years-ago/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/4-years-ago/</guid>
      <description>All of a sudden everybody in the Wechat moments started recalling what was life like 4 years ago, then I realized today is the leap day for every 4 years.
What was I like 4 years ago on the leap day? I was in Shenzhen, just came back from my hometown Yueyang where I lost my luggage in a cab a few weeks ago. I was very disappointed, I never thought someone would seriously take my luggage and don&amp;rsquo;t return back, I even didn&amp;rsquo;t lock it (I still don&amp;rsquo;t lock my luggage during trips, I&amp;rsquo;m just a lazy, careless guy).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review of the article &#34;The Feedback Fallacy&#34;</title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/the-feedback-fallacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/the-feedback-fallacy/</guid>
      <description>Here is the article The Feedback Fallacy Recently I read the article The Feedback Fallacy, I was amazed, I&amp;rsquo;ve thought it for a while, as I was raised in a traditional Asian culture which encourages submissiveness in a patriarchy way, I got a weak ego and incline to follow others whenever possible. But since I left my hometown and living alone in few metro cities for years, I found myself became more self-center, independent, and most importantly, happier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Post</title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 22:08:16 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/test-post/</guid>
      <description>Here is just some test text
what is funny isn&amp;rsquo;t funny</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/do-not-talk-who-are-bristle/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/do-not-talk-who-are-bristle/</guid>
      <description>I try not to discuss anything with people who are bristle To things not personal attack I total understand as human nature nobody is 100% objective, everyone is biased instead. Specially things like culture, religion or belief etc, those topics are too big for us as nonprofessional to talk about. But as daily trial random things, well, some of them could also be bound with years of life experience.
But my point is we try to be as objective as we can, put our ego aside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/girl-i-like/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/girl-i-like/</guid>
      <description>Girl I like in the first sight There are some kind of girls I know I&amp;rsquo;d love to get in touch if possible in the first sight, what are those characters attract me? Let me clean my thought by write it down.
docile &amp;amp; diffidence I first heard this two words phrase from the Video, that&amp;rsquo;s the common stereotype of Japanese girls which lots of people like, yeah, shame to say, I&amp;rsquo;m one of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/i-love-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/i-love-work/</guid>
      <description>I love my work I always heard people saying &amp;ldquo;work life balance&amp;rdquo;, as a bachelor, I don&amp;rsquo;t have much personal life, it&amp;rsquo;s hard for me separate work and life. I heard Jeff bezos says &amp;ldquo;Work life harmony&amp;rdquo;, yes, I&amp;rsquo;m totally down with that.
I got paid constantly with considerable salary It&amp;rsquo;s hard to deny programmers got paid very decently nowadays comparing other profession, the market is booming, lots of opportunities available all the time, it&amp;rsquo;s a good time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/i-turned-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/i-turned-30/</guid>
      <description>I turned 30 Age has been just a number for me since I known things. Because it doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean anything, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t bring or guarantee anything, I can&amp;rsquo;t say I&amp;rsquo;m better, smarter or wiser than you because I&amp;rsquo;m older, then why do we care? I treat it a general guidance, I know its existence, I respect it, but I don&amp;rsquo;t serious follow it. Until I passed the 30 years old threshold few months ago, I distinctly feel things became different.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/my-life-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/my-life-principles/</guid>
      <description>My life principles after 20s (version 0.1 in Mar 31 2020) As I&amp;rsquo;m a lifetime learner turned 30 years old, I&amp;rsquo;ve learned a lot. I&amp;rsquo;ve found some life principles work for me very well and I&amp;rsquo;d like to write them down to inspect and review them regularly.
Embrace English I can&amp;rsquo;t emphasis the importance of English since I&amp;rsquo;m living a country English is the official language, English ability would still one of my bottleneck for in few years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/my-role-model/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/my-role-model/</guid>
      <description>Adrian is my role model I&amp;rsquo;ve worked a handful of companies and numerous developers, Adrian is the dev who made the biggest impression on me, I&amp;rsquo;m very grateful I had the chance working with him closely. I deeply believe that I&amp;rsquo;m a good developer, but he is great, as the future I can forsee I hope I can become as great as him.
Work hard and get reward not only influencer, he is shaper he reads super fast</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/no-disturb-mode-shortcut/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/no-disturb-mode-shortcut/</guid>
      <description>The &amp;ldquo;No disturb mode&amp;rdquo; shortcut is a game changer  Pro user don&amp;rsquo;t care about Good User Experience
 As a self-professed pro user, I&amp;rsquo;ve been despising good UI/UX for years, I thought as long as it can its job well, it brings convenience or productivity, it doesn&amp;rsquo;t need (sometimes it just can&amp;rsquo;t) be very simple, straightforward or intuitive.
I&amp;rsquo;ve always known the feature &amp;ldquo;No disturb mode&amp;rdquo; in Mac which lots of people don&amp;rsquo;t know, it&amp;rsquo;s very nice feature, one click to stop all the notification from bothering.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/produce-with-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/produce-with-love/</guid>
      <description>Produce with Love 💖 I&amp;rsquo;ve used hundreds of Apps in Mac and iPhone, some of them are good, some are bad, some are extraordinary great which give me fresh ideas.
I&amp;rsquo;m impressed by the slogan of Spark email client, &amp;ldquo;Love your email again&amp;rdquo;, Yeah, Spark has done a fantastic job, I used to hate email like most of others feel, email is still play an essential role of our information and communication tool, it used to be great and appreciated by everybody, but more and more input and abusing, it just gets overwelcomed very easily, it&amp;rsquo;s so similar with our life, first we fall in love with something, we move all the possible focus and attentsion to it until it overwhelmed, then we don&amp;rsquo;t see the beautity of it, then start hate it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/taste-of-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/taste-of-free/</guid>
      <description>The taste of freedom People always saying the United States of America is a free country, but what does it mean &amp;ldquo;Free&amp;rdquo;, as I grew up in China and have lived here for 3+ years, I have some feelings of the freedom.
Freedom of press There are just tons of rumors and disinformation pumping out every second in the country. I think that&amp;rsquo;s just a side effect of free of expression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/the-enjoyment-partial-blindness/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/the-enjoyment-partial-blindness/</guid>
      <description>Don&amp;rsquo;t get strapped by rules Recently just few months ago I started riding motorcycle, I knew it was pretty scary riding bike in this grueling Bay Area, but I knew I gonna love it, it was so much fun hitting on the road in a fast speed without a iron wrapper enclosed, I can feel the wind and road. As a beginner, I need to practice a lot to get use to ride on the two wheels, and the best and most difficult motorcycle practicing place is mountain road, luckily, there is a curvy mountain road close to my house.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/thoughts-on-shawnshank-redemption/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/thoughts-on-shawnshank-redemption/</guid>
      <description>What I was touched by Shawnshank redemption Hope is a good thing, maybe the best thing in the world (with determination ) I&amp;rsquo;m not sure others, as for me, I&amp;rsquo;m really easy being touched by people made big success by long term continuse working, when I saw Andy open his arms in the raindrops embracing the baptism of new life after continuse dirty work in extremely condition, I was touched.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/tools-for-march/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/tools-for-march/</guid>
      <description>Tools for March I&amp;rsquo;ve always been fascinating by good tools, let me just record what tools I found amazed me and regret I didn&amp;rsquo;t try it later.
Footrest &amp;amp; toning ball for my stiff neck I&amp;rsquo;ve been suffered from neck stiffness for years, I knew it&amp;rsquo;s because my sedentary lifestyle, I can&amp;rsquo;t change it significantly. I did notice whenever I sit in front of my desk, my hands put on the surface of desk, the pressure either goes to my shoulder or I lay down more it goes to my lower back, no other way around.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/why-chinese-virus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/why-chinese-virus/</guid>
      <description>Why Trump keeps saying Chinese Virus in my opinion I&amp;rsquo;m not an expert on politics, actually on the contrary, I&amp;rsquo;ve very limited knowledge about politics, since I&amp;rsquo;ve just lived in the US for 3 years, I&amp;rsquo;m very amazed by the abundance of politic news and it really interact with our daily life which not a thing in China. But living in this country having so-called freedom of expression, I have every right to express my random opinion, I just want to write something down to help myself to understand things and improve my English writing ability incidentally.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/why-not-panic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/why-not-panic/</guid>
      <description>Why don&amp;rsquo;t they panic Recently with the CoronaVirus tension ramps up, I started thinking about buy some face masks just in case, but both offline shops and online retailers all out of stock. Shit, I&amp;rsquo;ve seen numerous news about those Chinese guys
They have the basic trust in Government and news media It&amp;rsquo; quite ironic people in China they trust and rely on government so much, but every time any dire situation happens, they got in panic very fast and started looking all kinds of rumors.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>