<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Journal on Alex&#39;s personal blog</title>
    <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/tags/journal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Journal on Alex&#39;s personal blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xieweialex.github.io/tags/journal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Monthly Journal January</title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/2024/monthly-jan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/2024/monthly-jan/</guid>
      <description>Table of Content What I&amp;rsquo;m thinking Year of visualization What happened Delights Struggle What I&amp;rsquo;m thinking The Meaning of Social I have never been a social person. Parties and social gatherings are rarely enjoyable for me, and I struggle to connect with others in those settings.
As I&amp;rsquo;ve grown older, I&amp;rsquo;ve come to realize the importance of breaking out of my friend/work cycle. It&amp;rsquo;s become clear to me that staying in this routine can be limiting, especially when I&amp;rsquo;m not satisfied with my current situation (which is often the case).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What I have been up to (Aug &amp; Sep)</title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/2023/august-stuff/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/2023/august-stuff/</guid>
      <description>Motivation for writing this I have always enjoyed sharing what I have learned, what excites me, and what I am pondering. However, more often than not, the people around me are not as enthusiastic about these topics as I am.
It is understandable, actually. We live in an information-overloaded world, where everyone has a constant feed of social media. I figured that I could write things down for my own future reference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I got my motorcycle back! ✌</title>
      <link>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/motorcycle-found/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://xieweialex.github.io/post/motorcycle-found/</guid>
      <description>How it started I got an internet call(anonymous call) at 11 am, I hesitated a few seconds to answer because most of those calls are just scams, but I took it. It was a female voice saying she is a police officer and my motorcycle is found and it&amp;rsquo;s in Fremont, she wanted me to stop by ASAP. I was like, What??!! 😮😮 I got ecstatic immediately, my bike has gone missing over 2 weeks, I&amp;rsquo;ve already crossed off my shopping list for my bike.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
